University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Meeting Records, 1964-2018; 4; 3.75 cubic ft.; 938 Digital Files
  - 2011-2012 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2011 July-2012 June
    - 2011-12 Schedules and Sign-ins - Sign-in Sheet.xls, 2012 May 30
  - 2010-2011 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2010 July-2011 June
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 09-27-10 Minutes Rev.doc, 2010 October 21
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 09-27-10 Minutes.doc, 2010 October 7
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 10-18-10 MinutesFinal.doc, 2010 November 18
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 11-15-10 Minutes.doc, 2010 December 13
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 12-13-10 Minutes.doc, 2011 March 1
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 2-14-11 Minutes.doc, 2011 March 31
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 3-14-11 Minutes.doc, 2011 May 12
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 4-11-11 Minutes.doc, 2011 May 10
    - 2010-11 Minutes-Approved - 5-9-11 Minutes.doc, 2011 September 30
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - Council on Academic Assessment overview fall 2010.pptx, 2010 August 31
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - CAA.pptx, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - CAFFECoR.pptx, 2010 August 19
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - COR.ppt, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - CPCA.ppt, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - GAC description.pptx, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - GOV.ppt, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - LISC.pptx, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - Orientation Agenda.doc, 2010 September 14
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - UAC.ppt, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - UFS presentation2.pptx, 2010 September 7
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - ULC overview.pptx, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Power Point Presentations - 2010-11 Orientation PPs - UPPC.ppt, 2010 September 20
    - 2010-11 Schedules and Sign-Ins - 2010-11 SEN SEC meeting schedule.doc, 2011 February 23
    - 2010-11 Schedules and Sign-Ins - 2010-11 Senate_schedule.doc, 2011 March 25
    - 2010-11 Schedules and Sign-Ins - 2010-11 Sign up.xls, 2010 September 29
    - 2010-11 Schedules and Sign-Ins - Senate Calendar.doc, 2011 March 16
    - 2010-11 Schedules and Sign-Ins - Senate Orientation Schedule.doc, 2010 July 30
    - 2010-11 Schedules and Sign-Ins - Senate Sign-in Sheet.xls, 2011 May 9
  - 2009-2010 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2009 July-2010 June
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - Leiva Letter.doc, 2010 June 2
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - 02-08-10_Agenda.doc, 2010 February 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - 020810 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES (2).doc, 2010 February 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - 12-14-09_Minutes (rmr2).doc, 2010 January 28
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - FAQs for the Revised General Education Program rev.doc, 2010 February 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - FW Gen Ed Resolution.msg, 2010 February 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - Lavallee's doc.doc, 2010 February 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - Proposed Gen Ed TF Senate resolution 2 8 2010.doc, 2010 February 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-08-10 - Rev. to HonProg in French Studies.doc, 2010 March 1
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - 03-08-10_Agenda (2).doc, 2010 March 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - 03-08-10_Agenda.doc, 2010 March 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - 030810 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES USen.doc, 2010 March 23
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - 0910-07 Revised absence policy (8).doc, 2010 March 3
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - FacultyEvaluation UFS 2005.pdf, 2010 March 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - Resolution on Faculty Eval of Admin (v2).doc, 2010 March 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - Summary of Binghamton Process.rtf, 2010 March 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-08-10 - UFS material re evaluation of administrators.doc, 2010 March 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 04-12-10_Agenda.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 0910-04 Grd Pt Reqrmt for Continuing in HC.doc, 2010 April 28
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 0910-08 Russian Deactivation MA and CAS Senate Bill.pdf, 2010 April 9
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 0910-09 Revised Policy re Minors.doc, 2010 April 9
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 0910-10 Policy for SU Grading.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 0910-11 Deletion of PJC.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 0910-12 Misconduct Policy.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - 36 Credit Degree Program Requirements.doc, 2010 April 9
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - April 12 10 senate chair report.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - Comparison of Present and Proposed CERS Policy Texts.pdf, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - Deactivation of RUS MA and Cert. of Advanced Study.msg, 2010 March 25
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - Gen Ed TF interim recommendation.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - OTHER UNIVERSITY.docx, 2010 April 9
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - Present CERS policy text.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - Proposed new CERS policy text.doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - Resolution on Faculty Eval of Admin (v3).doc, 2010 April 28
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-12-10 - UFS Executive Committee Resolution (rev 4).doc, 2010 April 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 05-10-10_Agenda.doc, 2010 May 7
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-10 Policy on SU Grading Rev.doc, 2010 April 23
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-13 Globalization Proposals Combined.doc, 2010 April 27
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-14 Organization Studies-PhD proposal.doc, 2010 May 7
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-15 Earth Atmospheric Sciences BA Admission Suspension.doc, 2010 May 10
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-16 CHM BS Chemistry-Materials Emphasis Program.doc, 2010 May 7
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-17 SPH-Suspend Minor in PH.doc, 2010 May 7
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - 0910-18 Deactvt CHM-BS Chemistry3-2 Program.doc, 2010 May 7
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - FAR Report 2010.pdf, 2010 April 22
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-10-10 - Provided by Provost at mtg.pdf, 2010 June 8
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-14-10 - 05-14-10_Agenda.doc, 2010 June 9
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - 050409 SenateMinutes.doc, 2009 October 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - 08-27 Smoke Free Campus Legislation (Senate Bill 0809-16) memo.pdf, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - 09-14-2009_SEC_Agenda.doc, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - 2009-10 COUNCILS AND COMMITTEES TO BE APPROVED 9-21-09.doc, 2011 May 31
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - 2009-2010 Senate Councils and Standing Committees - 9-14-09.xls, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - 9-21-09 Agenda.doc, 2010 August 2
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - Establishment of an Ombuds Office for Undergraduates.doc, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - GAC - 20090430092955533.pdf, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - GAC - Applied Chemistry (Forensic) Proposal.pdf, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - GAC - Communication MA Health Communication Concentration Proposal.pdf, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - GAC CCI Report 5_06_09.pdf, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - Request by CAS Dean 9 03 09.doc, 2009 September 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-21-09 - Senate chair report 9 21 09.doc, 2009 October 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-19-09 - 0910-01Credit Load.doc, 2009 October 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-19-09 - 10 19 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SEN .doc, 2009 October 21
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-19-09 - 10-19-09 Agenda (2).doc, 2009 October 26
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-19-09 - 10-19-09 Agenda.doc, 2009 October 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-19-09 - FYE_TF_Final_Report.pdf, 2009 October 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-19-09 - UNIVERSITY_FACULTY_SENATORS_REPORT_102209.doc, 2009 November 4
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 11-16-09 - 10-19-09 Minutes (RMR).doc, 2010 March 26
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 11-16-09 - 11-16-09 Agenda.doc, 2010 March 26
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-14-09 - 0910-02 PSM Certificate.pdf, 2010 March 15
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-14-09 - 0910-04 HONORS COLLEGE RETENTION STANDARDS (2).doc, 2009 December 14
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-14-09 - 0910-05 MUSIC MINOR REVISION.doc, 2009 December 14
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-14-09 - 12-14-09_Agenda REVISED (2).doc, 2010 January 22
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-14-09 - 12-14-09_Agenda REVISED.doc, 2009 December 14
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-14-09 - 121409 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.doc, 2009 December 14
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 010810 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.doc, 2010 March 15
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 020810 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES (2).doc, 2010 March 26
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 030810 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES USen.doc, 2010 May 10
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 041210 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES USEN.doc, 2010 April 12
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 051010 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SENATE.doc, 2010 May 10
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 10 19 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SEN .doc, 2009 October 29
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 11 16 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SENATE .doc, 2009 November 19
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - 9 21 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SEN .doc, 2009 October 6
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - Spring Plenary.doc, 2010 June 29
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - UNIVERSITY_FACULTY_SENATORS_REPORT_102209.doc, 2009 November 16
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - UNIVERSITY_FACULTY_SENATORS_REPORT_13010.doc, 2010 March 15
    - 2009-10 Agendas and Related Materials - 2009-10 Council Reports - ~$ 16 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SENATE .doc, 2009 December 1
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 02-08-10_Minutes (rmr edits).doc, 2010 March 1
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 02-08-10_Minutes (rmr) (2).doc, 2010 August 24
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 03-08-10_Minutes (draft).doc, 2010 March 31
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 03-08-10_Minutes (rmr edits).doc, 2010 April 7
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 03-08-10_Minutes (rmr).doc, 2010 April 13
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 04-12-10_Minutes (final).doc, 2010 August 24
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 04-12-10_Minutes (rmr edits).docx, 2010 April 29
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 05-10-10_Minutes (rmr edits).doc, 2010 June 10
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 05-10-10_Minutes final.doc, 2010 September 24
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 05-14-10_Minutes final.doc, 2010 September 24
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 10-19-09 Minutes (RMR).doc, 2009 November 20
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 11-16-09 Minutes.doc, 2009 November 30
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 12-14-09_Minutes (rmr2).doc, 2010 February 17
    - 2009-10 Minutes-Approved - 9-21-09 Minutes rmr.doc, 2009 October 13
    - 2009-10 Schedules and Sign-ns - 2009-10 Senate schedule.doc, 2009 September 22
    - 2009-10 Schedules and Sign-ns - Senate Sign-in Sheet.xls, 2010 May 5
  - 2008-2009 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2008 July-2009 June
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - 04-06-09 Senate Agenda.doc, 2009 April 7
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - 4 6 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SEN .doc, 2009 April 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - HonorsUACProposalUPDATED.doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - IRCUAP_Charter_amendment 3-30-09.doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - RE Proposed Suspension of Admission to MAPAP Program.msg, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - Resolution 1 MAPAP final to senate.doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - Senate_AGENDA-6April2009.doc, 2009 April 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - Senate_NOTES-6April2009.doc, 2009 April 27
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - April6 - ~$nate_NOTES-6April2009.doc, 2009 April 23
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - 12-15-08_Senate_AGENDA.doc, 2008 December 11
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - 12-15-2008-COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.doc, 2008 December 15
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - AMENDMT 0809-01 rev 10 30 08 .doc, 2008 December 15
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - AMENDMT 0809-02 (1a) (2).doc, 2008 December 11
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - Bill 0809-07 Chemistry Major.doc, 2008 December 12
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - cersbill.PDF, 2008 December 11
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - Charter Amend 0809-01 Eligibility to chair councils and committees.doc, 2008 December 15
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - misconuct_Policy_June_2008rev.PDF, 2008 December 15
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Dec15 - Senate Resolution-SEC approved version-9 Dec (3).doc, 2008 December 11
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - March9 - 02-09-09_Senate_AGENDA.doc, 2009 February 6
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - March9 - 03-09-09 Senate Agenda.doc, 2009 April 10
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - March9 - 3 09 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SEN .doc, 2009 June 17
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - March9 - Graduate Teaching Certificate Courses.xls, 2009 March 6
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - March9 - UNIVERSITY_FACULTY_SENATORS_REPORT_020509 (1) (2).doc, 2009 June 17
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - 09-034 PSY-BIO New UG Minor in Neuroscience (OT).doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - 5 4 09 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES SEN .doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - cersbill21.pdf, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - GAC.doc, 2009 May 4
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - Intnatl. Baccalaureate.doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - misconuct_Policy_05042009.pdf, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - misconuct_Policy_05042009_clean.pdf, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - Senate_AGENDA-4May2009.doc, 2009 May 1
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - Senate_Notes-4May2009.doc, 2009 May 26
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - SUNY Wide report (4).doc, 2009 May 5
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - UAC bill GPA Requirement for admission to the School of Ed minor.doc, 2010 August 3
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - UAC.doc, 2009 May 4
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - May4 - University at Albany Senate Resolution.doc, 2010 June 14
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Nov17 - 0809-05-UPC-DAES.doc, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Nov17 - 150-01-1 Effect of NYS budget on SUNY (2).doc, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Nov17 - 150-02-1 Implement Recommendations CHE.doc, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Nov17 - 150-03-1 Joint Committee TRansfer Articulation.doc, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Nov17 - 150-06-1 Diversity Cmte Resolution.doc, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Nov17 - CHE_Final-Report_Executive Summary.pdf, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Oct 20 - 10-20-08_Senate_AGENDA.doc, 2008 October 20
    - 2008-09 Agendas and Related Materials - Sept 22 - 09-22-08_Senate_AGENDA (2).doc, 2008 September 18
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 02-09-09_Senate_Minutes.doc, 2009 March 16
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 03-09-09 Senate Minutes.doc, 2009 April 7
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 04-06-09 Senate_Minutes-jwd.doc, 2009 May 5
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 050409 SenateMinutes (09-18).doc, 2009 September 21
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 050409 SenateMinutes jwd.doc, 2009 July 24
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 09-22-08_Senate_minutes.doc, 2009 August 6
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 10-20-08_Senate_minutes (2).doc, 2008 November 20
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 11-17-08_Senate_AGENDA (2).doc, 2008 November 17
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 11-17-08_Senate_Minutes.doc, 2009 January 8
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - 12-15-08_Senate_Minutes.doc, 2009 February 10
    - 2008-09 Minutes - Approved - Senate_Minutes-6April2009.doc, 2009 April 27
    - 2008-09 Power Point Presentations - 9-22-08 Chairs report.ppt, 2008 September 25
    - 2008-09 Power Point Presentations - Peer Review Process_0708-25-IRCAP ppt-May2008b.ppt, 2009 January 30
    - 2008-09 Schedules and Sign-ins - 2008-2009 SEN SEC meeting schedule.doc, 2009 March 11
    - 2008-09 Schedules and Sign-ins - 2008-2009 SENATE MEETING Schedule.doc, 2008 June 18
    - 2008-09 Schedules and Sign-ins - Senate Sign-in Sheet.xls, 2009 April 29
  - 2007-2008 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2007 July-2008 June
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 02-11-08 Senate Agenda.doc, 2008 February 14
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-10-08 Senate Agenda.doc, 2008 March 4
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-12-08 Senate Agenda.doc, 2008 May 9
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 05-16-08 Continuation Agenda.doc, 2008 May 16
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 09-24-07 Senate AGENDA d.doc, 2007 September 20
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 10-22-07 Senate Agenda.doc, 2007 October 17
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 11-26-07 Senate Agenda.doc, 2007 November 20
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 12-17-07 Senate Agenda.doc, 2007 December 17
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 4-14-08 Senate Agenda.doc, 2008 April 11
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2005-06 Council Summaries - March 20 COUNCIL SUMMARIES.doc, 2006 March 27
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 04-14-08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.doc, 2008 April 14
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 1 28 08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIESsec.doc, 2008 January 28
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 2 11 08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIESusen.doc, 2008 February 11
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 2 25 08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIESsec.doc, 2008 February 26
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 3 10 08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIESsen.doc, 2008 March 10
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 3 31 08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIESsec.doc, 2008 March 31
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - 2007-08 Council and Committee Summaries - 4 25 08 COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIESsec.doc, 2008 April 29
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - WORKING Minutes - 05-12-08 Senate Minutes.doc, 2008 October 1
    - 2007-08 Agendas and Related Materials - WORKING Minutes - 05-16-08 Senate Minutes.doc, 2008 May 21
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 03-10-08 Senate Mintues.doc, 2008 April 8
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 10-22-07 Senate Minutes.doc, 2007 November 20
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 11-26-07 Senate minutes.doc, 2007 December 13
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 12-17-07 Senate Minutes.doc, 2008 February 6
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 2-11-08 Senate Minutes.doc, 2008 February 21
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 4-14-08 Senate Minutes.doc, 2008 May 7
    - 2007-08 Minutes - Approved - 9-24-07 senate minutes(rhrc).doc, 2007 October 23
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - April 14, 2008 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2008 April 14
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - December 17, 2007 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2007 December 17
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - February 11, 2008 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2008 February 11
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - March 10, 2008 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2008 March 6
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - May 12, 2008 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2008 May 9
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - November 26, 2007 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2007 December 17
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - October 22, 2007 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2007 October 19
    - 2007-08 Power Point Presentations - September 24, 2007 SENATE MEETING.ppt, 2007 September 24
    - 2007-08 Schedules and Sign-ins - 2007-08 Orientation Schedule (2).xls, 2007 May 14
    - 2007-08 Schedules and Sign-ins - 2007-08 Orientation Schedule.xls, 2007 May 14
    - 2007-08 Schedules and Sign-ins - 2007-2008 SEN & SEC Meeting Schedule.doc, 2008 March 7
    - 2007-08 Schedules and Sign-ins - Orientation attendance sheet.xls, 2007 May 11
  - 2006-2007 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2006 July-2007 June
    - 2006-07 Agendas and Related Materials - 03-12-07 Senate Agenda.doc, 2007 March 8
    - 2006-07 Agendas and Related Materials - 04-16-07 Senate Agenda.doc, 2007 April 16
    - 2006-07 Agendas and Related Materials - 11-27-06 Senate Agenda.doc, 2006 November 22